Peter Fallon - Gallery Press collection, circa 1967-1998
Emory University
- Literary manuscripts, 1969-1998, Series 1; Boxes 1-111
  - Gallery Press author files, 1969-1998, Subseries 1.1; Boxes 1-85
    - Magee, Heno - "Red Biddy," TS with corrections (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Magee, Heno - "Red Biddy," TS (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, Book jacket material (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, Book jacket material (Box OP25)
    - Mahon, Derek, Correspondence, 1977-1988 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Mahon, Derek, Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Mahon, Derek, Correspondence, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Mahon, Derek, Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Mahon, Derek, Other published works (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Mahon, Derek, TS poems (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Mahon, Derek, Antarctica, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Mahon, Derek, Antarctica, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, Antarctica, Proofs (photocopy) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, Antarctica, TS with corrections (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, Antarctica, TS with corrections (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Bacchae, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Bacchae, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Bacchae, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Bacchae, TS with corrections (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Bacchae, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Bacchae, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Chimeras, Galleys (3 with corrections, 1 without corrections) (Box OP26)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Chimeras, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Chimeras, TS (photocopy) (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Mahon, Derek, Courtyards in Delft, Galley proof with corrections (Box OP27)
    - Mahon, Derek, Courtyards in Delft, TS with corrections (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Mahon, Derek, Courtyards in Delft, TS (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Mahon, Derek, Courtyards in Delft, TS (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Notes (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Proofs with corrections (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Proofs with corrections (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Proofs with corrections (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, Proofs (photocopy) (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, TS with corrections (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, High Time, TS (photocopy) (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, Proofs with corrections (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, Proofs with corrections (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, Proofs with corrections (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, TS (photocopy) (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, TS (incomplete) (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hudson Letter, TS (photocopy) (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Hunt by Night, TS (photocopy) (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Mock-ups with corrections (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Mock-ups with corrections (2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Mock-ups with corrections (1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Mock-ups with corrections (2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, Proofs (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, Journalism, TS with corrections (incomplete photocopy) (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, Proofs with corrections (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, Proofs with corrections (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, TS with corrections (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Mahon, Derek, Racine's Phaedra, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Mahon, Derek, The School for Wives, Mock ups (Box OP28)
    - Mahon, Derek, The School for Wives, Proofs with corrections (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Mahon, Derek, The School for Wives, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Sea in Winter, TS and page proofs (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, Proofs with corrections (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, Proofs with corrections (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, TS poems (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, Proofs with corrections (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Mahon, Derek, Selected Poems, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yaddo Letter, Mock-ups (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yaddo Letter, Proofs (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yaddo Letter, Proofs (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yaddo Letter, TS with corrections (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yaddo Letter, TS with corrections (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yaddo Letter, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, Proofs with corrections (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, Proofs with corrections (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, Proofs with corrections (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, Proofs (photocopy) (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, TS with corrections (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, TS with corrections (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Mahon, Derek, The Yellow Book, TS with corrections (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Correspondence, 1982-1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Other published works (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Mathews, Aidan, TS poems (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Exit/ Entrance, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Exit/ Entrance, Proofs with corrections (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Exit/ Entrance, Proofs with corrections (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Exit/ Entrance, TS with corrections (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Exit/ Entrance, TS with corrections (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Minding Ruth, Galleys (4 with corrections, 1 without corrections) (Box OP29)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Minding Ruth, Book jacket material (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Mathews, Aidan, Minding Ruth, TS with corrections (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Meehan, Paula, Correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Meehan, Paula, Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Meehan, Paula, Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Meehan, Paula, Other published works (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, Book jacket material (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, Book jacket material (Box OP30)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, Proofs with corrections (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, Proofs (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, TS poems (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, TS with corrections (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Meehan, Paula, The Man Who Was Marked by Winter, TS with corrections (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Meehan, Paula, Pillow Talk, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Meehan, Paula, Pillow Talk, TS with corrections (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Meehan, Paula, Pillow Talk, TS with corrections (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Meehan, Paula, Pillow Talk, TS with corrections (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John, Artwork by Evelyn Montague (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Montague, John, Biographical (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Montague, John, Book jacket material (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Montague, John, Corerspondence, 1977-1988 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Montague, John, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Montague, John, Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Montague, John, Correspondence, 1995 and undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Montague, John, Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Montague, John, Other published works (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Montague, John, TS poems (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Montague, John, TS stories with corrections (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Corrections (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Poems (1 of 5) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Poems (2 of 5) (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Poems (3 of 5) (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Poems (4 of 5) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Poems (5 of 5) (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (1 of 4) (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (2 of 4) (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (3 of 4) (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (4 of 4) (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (1 of 4) (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (2 of 4) (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (3 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (4 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (1 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (2 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (3 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (4 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (1 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (2 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (3 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John, Collected Poems, TS with corrections (4 of 4) (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Montague, John, "Crossing," TS poem (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Montague, John, Hill Field, Proofs (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Montague, John, Hill Field, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Montague, John, The Leap, TS and complete book (without cover) signed by author to Peter Fallon (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Montague, John, Mount Eagle, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Montague, John, Mount Eagle, Mock-ups with corrections (Box OP31)
    - Montague, John, Mount Eagle, TS poems (Box 62, Folder 4a)
    - Montague, John, Mount Eagle, TS with corrections (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Montague, John, Mount Eagle, TS with corrections (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Montague, John, New and Selected Poems, Book jacket material (Box OP32)
    - Montague, John, New Selected Poems, Proofs with corrections (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Montague, John, New Selected Poems, TS poems (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Montague, John, New Selected Poems, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John, New Selected Poems, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Montague, John, The Rough Field, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Montague, John, The Rough Field, Proofs (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Montague, John, Time in Armagh, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Montague, John, Time in Armagh, Proofs with corrections (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Montague, John, Time in Armagh, Proofs with corrections (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Montague, John, Time in Armagh, TS with corrections (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Montague, John, Time in Armagh, TS with corrections (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Book jacket material (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Other published works (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Other published works (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Muldoon, Paul, TS poems (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, Proofs with corrections (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, Proofs with corrections (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, TS (photocopy) (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, TS (photocopy) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Immram, TS with corrections (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Galley proofs with corrections (Box OP34)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Proofs (Box OP35)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Photographs (1 of 3) (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Photographs (2 of 3) (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Photographs (3 of 3) (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, Photographs (photocopy) (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Kerry Slides, TS (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Muldoon, Paul, "The O-O's Party New Year's Eve" (broadside), TS with corrections (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The O-O's Party New Year's Eve, book jacket mockup (Box OP33)
    - Muldoon, Paul, "The Point," (limited edition broadside) Mock-up (Box OP36)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Prince of the Quotidian, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Prince of the Quotidian, Proof with corrections (Box OP37)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Prince of the Quotidian, TS (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Muldoon, Paul, "Last Poems," [variant title of Quoof] TS (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Muldoon, Paul, "Midnight Swims," [variant title of Quoof] TS (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Muldoon, Paul, "Ambient Starlight," [variant title of Six Honest Serving Men] TS (photocopy) (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Six Honest Serving Men, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Six Honest Serving Men, Proofs with corrections (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Six Honest Serving Men, TS with corrections (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Six Honest Serving Men, TS (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Wishbone, Galley proofs with corrections (Box OP38)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Wishbone, Galley proofs (Box OP39)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Wishbone, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Muldoon, Paul, The Wishbone, TS (photocopy) (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Dervla [See Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Murphy, Liam, Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Murphy, Richard [See also: Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Murphy, Richard, Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Murphy, Richard, Other published works (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Murphy, Richard, TS poems (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Biographical (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Book jacket material (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Book jacket material (Box OP40)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Correspondence, 1976-1990 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Micellaneous (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Bailegangaire, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Bailegangaire, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Bailegangaire, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Blue Macushla, TS with corrections (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Blue Macushla, TS with corrections (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Thomas, "The White House," [variant title of Conversations on a Homecoming] TS with corrections (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Thomas, "The White House," [variant title of Conversations on a Homecoming] TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Conversations on a Homecoming, Mock-ups (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Conversations on a Homecoming, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Conversations on a Homecoming, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Conversations on a Homecoming, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Conversations on a Homecoming, Proofs with corrections (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Conversations on a Homecoming, TS with corrections (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Murphy, Thomas, A Crucial Week in the Life of a Grocer's Assistant, Proofs with corrections (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Thomas, A Crucial Week in the Life of a Grocer's Assistant, TS and MS with corrections (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Famine, Proofs with corrections (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Famine, Proofs with corrections (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Thomas, Famine, TS with corrections (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Gigli Concert, Galley proofs with corrections (Box OP41)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Gigli Concert, Galley proofs with corrections (3) (Box OP42)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Gigli Concert, TS with corrections (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Gigli Concert, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Thomas, "The Informer," TS with corrections (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Murphy, Thomas, On the Outside; On the Inside, Galley proofs with corrections (Box OP43)
    - Murphy, Thomas, On the Outside; On the Inside, TS with corrections (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Sanctuary Lamp, Galley proofs with corrections (Box OP44)
    - Murphy, Thomas, The Sanctuary Lamp, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Thomas, A Thief of a Christmas, TS with corrections' (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Murphy, Thomas, A Whistle in the Dark, Galley proofs with corrections (Box OP45)
    - Murphy, Thomas, A Whistle in the Dark, Acting edition with corrections (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Correspondence, 1980-1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Correspondence, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Other published works (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, TS poems (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Brazen Serpent, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Brazen Serpent, Proofs with corrections (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Brazen Serpent, Proofs with corrections (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Brazen Serpent, TS (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Brazen Serpent, TS (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Cork [See: Lalor, Brian] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, Proofs with corrections (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, Proofs with corrections (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, TS with corrections (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Magdalene Sermon, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Rose Geranium, TS poems with corrections (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Rose Geranium, TS with corrections (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, The Rose Geranium, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, 1977 book with MS corrections for reprint (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, Proofs with corrections (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, Proofs with corrections (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, Proofs with corrections (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, Proofs with corrections (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Second Voyage, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Site of Ambush, Book jacket material (Box OP46)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan, Site of Ambush, Proofs with corrections (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala [See also Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Biographical (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Book jacket material (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Other published works (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, The Astrakhan Cloak, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, The Astrakhan Cloak, Proofs with corrections (Box 70, Folder 12)